{
    "id": "c1b8e3f1ec9448c0a6815b80a2e1c3fc",
    "title": "Commonly Confused Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is a great museum. Thanks for …………….. me here.",
            "description": "We use bring for movements to the places where the speaker or hearer is.",
            "answers": [
                "taking",
                "bringing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Put on your coat. I am ……………. you to the doctor.",
            "description": "We use bring for movements to the places where the speaker or hearer is. Take is used for movements to other places.",
            "answers": [
                "taking",
                "bringing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. me your book for a minute, will you?",
            "description": "Lend is like give. So lend me means give me.",
            "answers": [
                "Lend",
                "Borrow"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened to that camera you ……………… from me?",
            "description": "Borrow is like take",
            "answers": [
                "lent",
                "lend",
                "borrowed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They live in a very …………… street.",
            "description": "Wide is used to indicate the physical distance from one side of something to the other.",
            "answers": [
                "wide",
                "broad",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a tall guy with …………. shoulders.",
            "description": "Broad is used in some common expressions like broad shoulders and broad daylight.",
            "answers": [
                "wide",
                "broad"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie was not very interesting but ……………. the acting was superb.",
            "description": "We use ‘on the other hand’ to give the other side of a question.",
            "answers": [
                "on the contrary",
                "on the other hand",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I suppose the movie was very interesting.’ ‘…………….., it was a total waste of time.’",
            "description": "On the contrary is used to contradict – to say that what has just been said is not true or correct.",
            "answers": [
                "On the other hand",
                "On the contrary",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "So far 100 people ……………… in the riots.",
            "description": "Died is the past participle of die. Dead is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "have died",
                "have dead"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody helped me ………………. him.",
            "description": "Except means other than.",
            "answers": [
                "except",
                "without",
                "but for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… his support, I would have failed.",
            "description": "Without and but for are possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "Without",
                "But for",
                "Except"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This jacket does not …………… me. Have you got a smaller size?",
            "description": "Fit refers to size and shape. ",
            "answers": [
                "fit",
                "suit",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}